Hyungrok Kim

https://rokrokss.com

: https://github.com/q0115643

t: +821089595643

e: hyungrok.kim@kaist.ac.kr

PROFILE

Unexperienced but passionated student developer anticipating for the first job to open my career. Belonged in Industrial Design department for 2 years, moved to Computer Science 2 years ago. Studied Data Science and NLP trying to understand the linguistic communication of emotions. Believes firmly that I will relish working as a web developer and serve people with better lives.

WORK EXPERIENCES

PLAYSOLUTION (http://povi.co.kr/)

Intern, Frontend Developer

Design and Develop Web Dashboard used tomanage exchanges between content-providers, store-owners, distributers.

Angular2, Typescript

Jul 2017 - Aug 2017

Dajeon, Republic of Korea

UILAB(http://uilab.kr/)

Undergraduate Researcher

Study on Metaphor Comperhension

Jul 2018 - Dec 2018

Dajeon, Republic of Korea

ORGANIZATION

Korea Design Membership(http://kidp.or.kr)

Attend various design classes

Mar 2016 - Feb 2018

EDUCATION

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology

B.S. in Computer Science Minor in Industrial Design

Mar 2014 - Present

Daejeon, Korea

CORSEWORKS

CS Major

CS574 Natural Language Processing CS570 Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning CS492 Introduction to Machine Learning CS474 Text Mining CS470 Introduction to Artificial Intelligence CS330 Operating Systems and Lab CS320 Programming Language **CS311 Computer Organization** CS300 Introduction to Algorithms CS230 System Programming

Others

ID307 Interface Design **ID220 Interaction Prototyping** ID302 Space Design **ID301 Product Design Factors** ID219 Computer-Aided Design ID214 Digital Design Graphics **ID213 Product Design Fundamentals** ID212 Three-Dimensional Design ID217 Presentation Technique **ID218 Photo Techniques** ID215 Introduction to Industrial Design MAS109 Introduction to Linear Algebra MAS205 Probability and Statistics

PROJECTS

REST Countries



https://naranara.net

Simple react webpage of listing various country information.

React, Redux, Typescript, Webpack, Babel, Sass May 2019

ROKUROKU

CS206 Data Structure

CS204 Discrete Mathematics



https://rokuroku.work

Build web to show japanese old short-comics to viewers but mainly for my personal web development practice.

Django, React, Create-React-App, JavaScript, Sass, Nginx, uWSGI, Docker Mar 2019 - Apr 2019

Arithmetic Hash



Build LSTM-based query encoder designed to replace the hash algorithm of p2p network

Pytorch, RNN, Markov Model Jan 2019

Neural Poetry Scansion



Based on Original Paper (Proceedings of AAAI 2016) deep-learning apporach to improve performance on poety-analysis

Pytorch, BiLSTM-CRF, Word2Vec May 2018 - Aug 2018

GCN-RNNG based Korean NMT



Syntax-Aware Model for Neural Machine Translation with Morpheme Structure in Korean

Pytorch, SyntaxNet, GCN, RNNG, KoNLPy, Word2Vec May 2018 - Aug 2018

HarmonyTable



Hardware project of combining harmony & turntable in Interaction Prototyping

Arduino

Sep 2016 - Oct 2016

FlyDuck



Rich Context Competition

https://coleridgeinitiative.org/richcontextcompetition





Deep Learning based model to comprehend scientific researches extract research fields, methods, and dataset usages

Pytorch, ELMo, BiLSTM-CRF, Word2Vec

Nov 2018 - Dec 2018

Tangible Interface Game

Processing, Arduino

Nov 2016 - Dec 2016